Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You can do well, right?
よくやれるでしょ?
It's not said much.
あんまり言われないです
Really?
本当に?
That's definitely a lie.
絶対嘘だ
It's really not said.
本当に言われません
It's not hard.
硬くなですね
Are you nervous?
緊張してるかな?
Yes, I do.
はい、してます
You're doing amazing.
すごいしてるよね
I want to relieve your stress, so is it okay if I talk to you for about 5 hours?
緊張解きたいんで、5時間ぐらいお話ししても大丈夫ですか?
5 hours is a bit...
5時間はちょっと...
Is it a little long?
ちょっと長いかな?
It's too long.
長すぎです
Do you have a pretty weak butt?
結構お尻弱いですか?
Is it weak?
弱いかな?
I see.
なるほどね
Shortcuts look good on you.
ショートカット似合いますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is it always short?
ずっとショートなの?
It was long.
ロングでした
How far did you extend it?
どれぐらいまで伸ばしたの?
That's it so far.
ここまでありました
Did it grow that much?
そんなに伸びてたの?
yes.
はい
It doesn't seem to change the impression at all.
全然印象変わりそうだね
I agree.
そうですね
Did something happen?
何かあってきたんですか?
I'm bald.
はげてきちゃって
That's not true.
そんなことないでしょ
I was really bald.
本当に、はげてきちゃいました
It's so far off.
これぐらいずれしちゃったもんね
I don't have time.
ちゃいません
Is it a bit stressful?
なんかちょっとストレスかな?
Is it stress?
ストレスかな?
kana?
かな?
Well, that's right.
まあね、そうなんだ
it's okay.
大丈夫です
She wears it less than me.
僕より着てないです
Let's do our best together.
お互い頑張りましょうね
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Is it okay if I ask you a lot of questions?
何かいろいろ質問していっても平気かな?
What do you do on your days off?
休みの日とか何してるのかな?
I take walks on my days off.
休みの日は散歩してます
Where are you walking?
どこ散歩してるの?
river.
川
I'm taking a walk along the river.
川を散歩してます
Does that mean you should bring your dog with you?
それはワンちゃんとか連れてってこと?
that's right.
そうです
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, do you like walking?
じゃあ、お散歩が好きなのか?
that's right.
そうです
When you walk with your dog and he/she calls out to you,
一緒にワンちゃんと歩いて声かけられるとき、
What kind of response will you take?
どんな対応になるの?
What will happen?
どうなる?
This kid is cute, I asked.
この子かわいいね、みたいに聞いたら
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I'm not quite shy.
結構、人見知りではないんだ
I can speak quite well.
結構ちゃんと話せるんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, what type of guy is he?
そしたら、男の人のタイプは?
type of man.
男の人のタイプ
Do you have an appearance or what kind of person you like?
外見とか、どういう人が好きとかある?
kind person.
優しい人
Also, I like Iida-san from Breaking Down.
あとは、 ブレイキングダウンに出てた飯田さんが好きです
A slightly scary person came.
ちょっと怖い人来ちゃったけど
Is he a good-looking guy?
イケメンなのかな?
It's cool.
かっこいいです
Really.
めっちゃ
It's cool.
かっこいいです
Wait, do you mean someone who likes martial arts?
ちょっとじゃあ、格闘法みたいな人ってこと?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Well, I like people who are pretty strong.
じゃあ、結構強い人が好きなんだ
No, that's not the case.
いや、そんなことはないんですけど
That person has an amazing face.
その人が顔がすごいタイプなんだ
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうです
Face and body?
顔と体?
What kind of body do you have?
どういう体してるの?
I'm muscular.
ムキムキです
Surprisingly, I like that kind of thing.
意外にそういう系好きなんだ
I like it.
好きです
So, it's better to have people's expectations.
じゃあ、人は期待ってもらった方が、
Do men like it when they have expectations?
男の人は期待ってもらった方が好きなんですか?
yes.
はい
That's right.
そうなんだ
yes.
はい
So, is it macho at all?
で、 マッチョ全然あり?
Yes.
ありです
There are so many.
めっちゃありです
yes.
はい
So what do you mean you prefer just us?
じゃあ、我々だけの方が好きってことは?
Well, I prefer that.
まあ、そっちの方が好きです
And he has a kind personality.
で、性格は優しい
So, the person who said that earlier, Mr. Iida?
じゃあ、そのさっき言った人、 飯田さん?
Where would you like to go on a date?
デ ート行くならどこ行きたいですか?
Eh, Kyoto?
えー、京都?
I want to go to Kyoto.
京都行きたいです
The pinpoint has arrived again.
またピンポイントが来たね
Yes, yes, yes.
はい、はい、はい
What should I do when I go to Kyoto?
京都行ってどうするの?
I want to go to Kyoto and wear kimono together on a date.
京都行って、一緒に着物着てデートしたいです
But it looks good in a kimono.
でも着物似合いそうだね
is that so?
そうですか?
I think it looks great on you.
すごい似合うと思います
What color kimono do you want to wear?
何色の着物着たいの?
What color?
何色?
Bright red?
真っ赤?
A kimono-like kimono, or something light.
着物っぽい着物か、 淡い感じの、
Cute guy.
可愛いやつ
When you say pale, do you mean light blue?
淡い感じって水色とかってこと?
Light blue or pink.
水色とかピンクとか
It seems like both would suit you.
どっちも似合いそうですね
It seems like the atmosphere is changing.
なんか雰囲気変わりそうでね
I see.
なるほど
Where would you like to go for dinner together?
一緒にご飯とかどこ行きたいの?
Do you only eat the skin of the eight legs?
八つ足の皮だけ食べるの?
Eh, rice?
えー、ご飯?
Eh, where is it?
えー、どこだろう?
Eh, rice?
えー、ご飯?
Kyoto cuisine?
京都料理?
Japanese food?
和食?
I want to eat luxurious Japanese food.
豪華な和食食べたいです
I see.
なるほどね
If we go on a trip together, is it okay to go on a trip for the first date?
一緒に旅行行っちゃったらさ、 初デートは旅行でいいの?
No.
ダメです
Where do you want to go on your first date?
初デートはどこ行きたいの?
The first date...
初デートは...
Please be cute.
可愛がいてお願いします
There's cuteness...
可愛がいて...
First date...
初デート...
Hey, first date.
へー、初デート
What is it?
何ですかね?
A stylish restaurant?
おしゃれなご飯屋さん?
I see.
なるほど
What do you want to eat?
何食べたいの?
together...
一 緒に...
There's a lot of things like yakiniku and sushi, right?
焼肉とか寿司とかさ、いろいろあるじゃん?
Hmm...
んー...
Monger?
モンジャー?
It's Japanese.
和ですね
I like Monger.
モンジャーが好きです
Let's eat Monger together...
一緒にモンジャー食べて...
Well, maybe it's the first breakup?
まぁ、1回目解散かな?
It's disbanded.
解散です
We will go to Kyoto together from the second time.
2回目から一緒に 京都行っちゃいますと
Is it a little early for the second time?
ちょっと2回目は早い?
It's early.
早いです
Third time?
3回目?
early.
早い
Is it the fourth time?
4回目かな?
Hmm, it's still early.
うーん、まだ早い
Fifth time?
5回目?
Okay, maybe it's not that big of a deal.
いいだろ、そんなに多房かもしれないよ
This is Tafusa.
多房です
I'm Tafusa, really.
多房です、めっちゃ
I don't know though.
わからないけど
No matter how many times I went on a date, even if I was invited to a hotel, I didn't want to go.
何回目のデートからさ、 ホテルとか誘われても 行かなくて思
Do you want to spend money?
った りするの?
About the 10th time.
10回目くらい
Huh?
えっ?
1 month later?
1ヶ月後?
It's solid.
固いですね
It's hard.
固いです
So, how do you think it would be good to be invited?
じゃあ、どういうふうに誘われて いいと思う?
I've never been invited...
今まで誘われてさ...
Have you ever been invited?
今まで誘われて?
Hmm...
うーん...
Is there a situation that you dream of?
憧れのシチュエーションとかあったりする?
A dream situation?
憧れのシチュエーション?
I'd like to be proposed to at a fancy restaurant.
なんかオシャレなご飯屋さんで プロポーズされたいです
Proposal?
プ ロポーズ?
I see.
なるほどね
A proposal?
プロポーズか
I said it a while ago.
だいぶ先言っちゃいましたけど
What do you think?
どう なの?
Do you like edges?
エッジが好きなのかな?
I like it.
好きです
好きなんだ
Yes, yes.
うん、はい
Which is S or M?
SとMってどっちなの?
S and M?
SとM?
Are S and M M?
SとMはMかな?
It's M.
Mです
Do you do it to women or yourself?
女にとか自分でしたりするの?
I don't.
しないんですよ
What do you do when you're horny?
ムラムラしたらどうしてる?
If you get horny...
ムラムラしたら...
Eh, how are you doing?
えーどうしてる?
I'm horny...
ムラムラする...
Not much?
あんましない?
Yeah, not really.
うん、あんましないです
Don't you ever feel lonely?
寂しくなったりもしないの?
I do get lonely sometimes.
寂しくなったりはします
What do you do when you feel lonely?
寂しくなったらどうするの?
What should I do?
どう する?
forget.
忘れる
You don't even call anyone?
誰かに電話したりもしないんだ?
I don't.
しないです
What did you do?
何をした?
I've never had one before, but I like the edge.
あんましたことないけど、 エッジが好きなんだ
Tell me about the most exciting edge you've ever had.
今まででさ、 興奮したエッジを教えてよ
Excited Edge?
興奮したエッジ?
Can I tell you what I heard?
聞いた話でもいいですか?
Ah, okay.
あ、いいです
That's what I want to do.
それ自分がやってみたいってことだね
that's right.
そう です
It was a hotel with a beautiful view, and fireworks were going off right in front of me.
景色が綺麗なホテルで、 目の前に花火が上がってて、
Have sex on the balcony.
ベランダでセックスする
I see.
なるほどね
Does it feel open?
開放的な感じの?
At a luxury inn, fireworks were going off right in front of me.
高級旅館で、 目の前で花火が上がってて、
Have sex on that balcony.
そのベランダで セックスする
It's quite edgy.
結構エッジですね
I see.
なるほど
If you rush to such a place,
確かにそういう場所に急いだったら、
It might be okay to stay in Kyoto.
その まま京都でもいいかもね
I'm sorry, but it's not available for commission.
申し訳ないけど、 委託にありません
I called him, but it was due to his smoking schedule.
呼んだんですけど、 タバコスケジュールのため
sorry.
すみません
It's a feeling.
気持ちね
There are some people who might come out, so stay nearby.
出てきそうな人もいるんで、近くに
Looks like it's down somehow.
なんとかダウンみたいなね
There are some people who are likely to come out.
出てきそうな人もいるんで
yes.
はい
I'll prepare,
準備するんで、
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Did you do warm-up exercises?
準備体操もしたかな?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
I'll check if I can do the warm-up exercises properly.
ちゃんと準備体操できて、確認するかな?
Is it okay if I pat you on the head?
頭撫でても平気かな?
How about a pat on the head?
頭撫でてもどうですか?
I like it.
好きです
It's cute how she looks a little shy,
なんかちょっと恥ずかしがってる感じがかわいいんで、
It might be a little embarrassing, but I thought it would be okay to ask.
ちょっと恥ずかしいかも、 お願いしてもいいかなと思ってる
So.
んで
It might be embarrassing.
恥 ずかしいかも
Can I give you a little blowjob with my fingers?
指でちょっとフェラしてもらっていいですか?
With my fingers.
僕の指で
Ears?
耳とか?
ears or neck.
耳とか首とか
I like it.
好きです
好きなんだ
Maybe?
多分かい?
It ends up looking something like that.
みたいな感じになっちゃうけど
Hey, can I press it again?
ちょっと ね、押し直していいですか?
There is.
あるんだね
Surprisingly.
意外に
Oh, it's big
あ、おっきい
hey.
ね
How about this?
これ どう?
tickles?
くすぐったい?
It's ticklish, really.
くすぐったいです、めっちゃ
It's not like it's tickling and it feels good,
くすぐった気持ちいいみたいな感じじゃなくて、
tickles?
くすぐったい?
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Like this?
こうやって?
It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
It's long.
長いです
But yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
でもね、楽しみだね
Because it's Matsumon.
まつもんだからね
Cute underwear.
かわいい下着
I'm wearing fashionable underwear.
おしゃれな下着履いてる
Is it your favorite?
お気に入りなの?
It's my favorite.
お気に入りです
I'm speechless.
言 葉を失っちゃうね
Because it's cute.
かわいいから
Is it cute?
かわいいですか?
Is this tickling?
これはくすぐったい?
This feels good.
これは気持ちいいです
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
yes.
はい
It's like this.
こういう感じなんだ
I feel like I can just wear it like this.
このままペロンと着る感じなんだ
yes
そう
is.
です
What color underwear are you wearing?
どう いう色味の下着履いてるの?
I agree.
そうですね
I wonder what it is
なんだろう
hey.
ね
This is coming.
これ くるじゃん
It's not okay.
いいんじゃないです
Hey, just guide me.
ちょっとさ、誘導してよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's right, look here.
そうそう、こっち見て
You think it's going to take a lot, right?
めっちゃ取るじゃんって思ってるでしょ?
Do you think it will take a lot?
めっちゃ取るじゃんって思ってる?
I'm thinking.
思ってます
I want you to stand up and be in your underwear.
立ってさ、 下着姿になってほしいんだよ
立って下着姿になってほしいんだよ
Come out slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり出て
I like the tiles.
タイルいいね
dirty.
汚い
Can I share it with you for about an hour?
1時間ぐらい分け取っていい?
No.
ダメです
Can I have 5 seconds?
5秒取っていい?
If it's 5 seconds.
5秒なら
No.
ダメです
Shall we make peace together?
一緒にピースしようか
Seino.
せーの
It's cute.
かわいいね
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
I took it.
取っちゃいました
Can you go?
いける?